Guide to the United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia Records
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Related Organizations and Publications, Series VI
  - Publications
    - Related to education, 1923
      - Universal Education in China by Tse-hsiung Kuo, Council of International Affairs, 1936 (Box 457, Folder 6093)
      - Miscellaneous magazine and newspaper articles related to the China Colleges, 1935-1949 (Box 457, Folder 6094-6096)
      - "Chinese Universities and the War" by Oliver J. Caldwell, 1942 (Box 456, Folder 6085)
    - Related to medical work and medical education
      - Occasional Leaflet, Council on Medical Mission, Chinese Medical Association, 1934, 1938, 1947 (Box 458, Folder 6097)
      - "Medical Education" in China by Randolph T. Shields, 1936 (Box 458, Folder 6097)
      - Typescript and mimeographed material, 1938-1948, n.d. (Box 458, Folder 6098)
    - Related to missionary activity and religion in China
      - The Amazing Chinese by Willis Lamott, 1940 (Box 458, Folder 6099)
      - Calendar from Szechwan, West China, 1940 (Box 458, Folder 6099)
      - China Marches Toward the Cross by Earl Cressy, 1938 (Box 458, Folder 6099)
      - "Christianity in China" by Hollington K. Tong, 1957 (Box 458, Folder 6099)
      - "The Day of Small Things", being an outline of the beginning of cooperative church work in the city of Nanking, ca. 1922 (Box 458, Folder 6099)
      - "For the Love of Man" by George E. Sokolsky, 1938 (Box 458, Folder 6100)
      - "The Gripsholm" by George E. Sokolsky, 1943 (Box 458, Folder 6100)
      - The Jesus I Know by Y.T. Wu, T. Z. Koo and E. R. Hughes, 1930 (Box 458, Folder 6100)
      - Missions in War by M. Searle Bates, n.d. (Box 458, Folder 6100)
      - My Religion by Madame Chiang Kai-shek, 1934 (Box 458, Folder 6100)
      - Willow Pattern by Winifred Galbraith, 1933 (Box 458, Folder 6100)
      - "Winning Chinese Youth to Christ", B.D. thesis of Ellen M. Studley, 1956 (Box 458, Folder 6101)
    - Related to the teaching of English as a second language
      - Descriptive English Grammar and Exercises for Chinese Students by Anne Cochran (UBCHEA publication), 1955 (Box 458, Folder 6102)
      - English Pronunciation for Chinese Students by Anne Cochran and Lin Yu Keng (UBCCC publication), 1954 (Box 458, Folder 6103)
      - "The English Record, First Series" Issues 1,2,3, 1956-1958 (Box 459, Folder 6104)
      - Mastery of English Book II by H. B. Graybill, 1923 (Box 459, Folder 6105)
      - Modern Methods of Teaching English as a Foreign Language by Anne Cochran (UBCCC publication), 1952 (Box 459, Folder 6106)
    - Miscellaneous
      - "America's Investment in Chinese Friendship" by Oliver J. Caldwell, 1938 (Box 459, Folder 6107)
      - The Chinese College Song Book compiled by Elam J. Anderson, 1923 (Box 459, Folder 6107)
      - The Chinese Woman and Four Other Essays by Sophia Chen, 1934 (Box 459, Folder 6107)
      - On Foot to Freedom by Rev. Newton Chiang, 1939 (Box 459, Folder 6107)
      - The Pagoda - Chinese songs compiled by Bliss Wiant, 1946 (Box 459, Folder 6107)
      - "Personal and Professional Problems of Chinese Students and Former Students in the New York Metropolitan Area" - Ph.D. dissertation of Samuel Shi-shin Kung, 1955 (Box 459, Folder 6108)
      - "This is China: Portrait of a Nation" by Gerald F. Winfield, 1949 (Box 459, Folder 6109)
      - Woman's Place in Chinese History by Hu Shih, ca. 1939 (Box 459, Folder 6109)
      - Maps of China and cities therein (Box 459, Folder 6110)
- Complete List of Oversize Material, Oversize
  - Associated Boards for Christian Colleges in China
    - Scrapbook re. China Colleges Conferences (Box OV11-A1)
    - Photos of Annual meetings, China Colleges Conference (Box OVd7)
  - United Board for Christian Colleges in China
    - Consolidation of Boards, 1945 (Box OVd7)
    - Amendment to Charter: increasing scope of Board activities, 1951 (Box OVd7)
    - Amendment to Charter: change of name to UBCHEA, 1956 (Box OVd7)
    - Film: "The Frontline of Democracy", 1947 (Box OV11-B3)
  - United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia
    - Cash disbursements Recordbook, 1956-1957 (Box OV11-A2)
  - Fukien Christian University
    - Provisional charter, 1918 (Box OVd7)
    - Recognition by University of State of New York, 1922 (Box OVd7)
    - Amendment to Charter, 1923 (Box OVd7)
    - Absolute charter, 1934 (Box OVd7)
    - Blueprints and Architectural drawings (Box OVd7)
  - Ginling College
    - Charter, 1935 (Box OVd8)
    - Charter verification, 1961 (Box OVd8)
    - Diploma of Dju Luh, 1924 (Box OVd8)
    - Blueprints (Box OVd8)
    - 3 photograph albums related to Ginling Alumnae Association (Box OV11-C2–OV11-C4)
    - Miscellaneous photographs (Box OV11-D)
    - Miscellaneous photographs (Box OVd1)
    - Photographs Vol. III: Miscellaneous (Box OV11-V)
    - Phonograph records (2) - "Chinese College Women in War Time" - Produced by Ginling College 25th Anniversary Committee (with CD version) (Box OV11-V)
  - Hangchow Christian College
    - Framed photograph (Box OVd9)
  - Huachung (College) University
    - Financial Record Book, 1948-1957 (Box OV11-C1)
  - Hwa Nan College
    - Provisional charter, 1922 (Box OVd8)
    - Absolute charter, 1934 (Box OVd8)
  - Lingnan University
    - Photographs (Box OV11-E)
  - Nanking, University of
    - Amendment to Charter, 1923 (Box OVd8)
    - Absolute Charter, 1934 (Box OVd8)
    - Microfilm of student records (Box OV11-F7)
    - Blueprints, architectural drawings, maps (Box OVd8, Box OV11-F1–OV11-F3)
    - Photograph album (Box OV11-S)
    - Loose photographs (Box OVd8)
  - Shantung Christian University (Cheeloo)
    - Blueprints, architectural drawings (Box OVd7, Box OV11-F4–OV11-F6)
    - 2 cases of lantern slides (Box OV11-G)
    - Loose photographs (Box OV11H)
  - West China Union University
    - Provisional charter, 1922 (Box OVd9, Box OV11-i2)
    - Absolute charter, 1934 (Box OVd9, Box OV11-i2)
    - Blueprints and architectural drawings (Box OV11-i2, Box OVd15)
    - Rolled photographs (Box OV11-i2)
    - Loose photographs (Box OV11H)
  - Yenching University
    - Certificate of Incorporation of the Trustees of Peking Univeristy, 1890 (Box OV11-i1)
    - Amendments to Charter, 1928,1929, 1937 (Box OV11-i1)
    - Diploma for Wang T'ung, 1933 (Box OVd9)
    - Financial Record book, 1929-1949 (Box OV11-i2)
    - Blueprints, architectural drawings, maps (Box OVd9, Box OV11-J1–OV11-J5)
    - Photograph album (Box OV11-L)
    - Photograph album (Box OV11-M)
    - Photograph album (Box OV11-N)
    - Framed and loose photographs (Box OV11-O)
    - 3 framed photographs (Box OV11-P1)
    - Loose photographs (Box OV11-Q)
    - Photographs and captions in display format (Box OV11-R)
  - Central China College
    - Blueprints (Box OVd9)
  - Tunghai University
    - Blueprints (Box OVd9)
  - Miscellaneous maps (Box OV11-T)
  - Miscellaneous photos of China (Box OV11H)
  - Princeton-Yenching charter (Box OVd9)